<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Bad Luck Cookie</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">Bad Luck Cookie</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Bad Luck Cookie</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>

    <string name="hello_first_fragment">Bad Luck Cookie</string>
    <string name="hello_second_fragment">Bad Luck Cookie</string>
    <!--NUESTOS STRINGS-->
    <string-array name="malas_frases">
        <item>I cannot help you, for I am just a cookie</item>
        <item>If at first you dont succeed, destroy all evidence that you tried</item>
        <item>Happy? It wont last!</item>
        <item>Its good to donate your brain to science but shouldnt you have waited till you died?</item>
        <item>At least I believe in you. Me, a piece of paper/pixels</item>
        <item>Feel free to waste the day away. It makes no difference in your case</item>
        <item>When life knocks you down, just stay down</item>
        <item>Your first love hasnt forgotten you - still wondering how one could be so stupid!?</item>
        <item>At your wedding, everyone will be dressed in black</item>
        <item>Maybe its time for another therapy session?!</item>
        <item>You are as welcome here as a fart in a spacesuit</item>
        <item>You are uncharismatic, impolite and unattractive. Were you really expecting good news?</item>
        <item>Sadly, its possible to be going both forwards and downhill</item>
        <item>Looks like your luck is running out - and far, far away from you</item>
        <item>Your wishes dont even come true at Christmas</item>
        <item>Today you are on the edge of the abyss. Tomorrow you will have taken a big step forward</item>
        <item>As an outsider, what do you think of the human race?</item>
        <item>Things will get better, something, maybe</item>
        <item>Only idiots believe these prophecies</item>
        <item>Praise the goal and a nightmare you have will come true</item>
        <item>Put trust in people who are going to lift you higher - it may doom you</item>
        <item>Error 404: Fortune not found</item>
        <item>You have just eaten poison</item>
        <item>Your pet is planning to eat you</item>
        <item>Bad luck and misfortune will infest your pathetic soul for all eternity</item>
        <item>Have a bad day? Try to open another cookie again</item>
        <item>We have just hacked your router</item>
        <item>You will die alone</item>
        <item>A dark haired woman will soon be giving you a gift</item>
        <item>the greatest danger could be your stupidity</item>




    </string-array>

    <string-array name="buenas_frases">
        <item>The early bird gets the worm, but the second mouse gets the cheese.</item>
        <item>Be on the alert to recognize your prime at whatever time of your life it may occur.</item>
        <item>Your road to glory will be rocky, but fulfilling.</item>
        <item>Courage is not simply one of the virtues, but the form of every virtue at the testing point.</item>
        <item>Patience is your alley at the moment. Don’t worry!</item>
        <item>Nothing is impossible to a willing heart.</item>
        <item>Don’t worry about money. The best things in life are free.</item>
        <item>Don’t pursue happiness – create it.</item>
        <item>Courage is not the absence of fear; it is the conquest of it.</item>
        <item>Praise possibilities of improvement and a dream you have will come true</item>
        <item>Praise the goal - you are heading in the right direction</item>
        <item>Focus on possibilities of improvement - it can pay off in most satisfying ways</item>
        <item>Praise whatever makes you happy - good things will happen</item>
        <item>You cannot love life until you live the life you love.</item>
        <item>One that would have the fruit must climb the tree.</item>
        <item>Of all our human resources, the most precious is the desire to improve.</item>
        <item>We must always have old memories and young hopes.</item>
        <item>A person who won’t read has no advantage over a person who can’t read.</item>



    </string-array>
    <string name="fab_description">A fab icon with no use for now</string>
    <string name="frase_mala_1">Vas a tener muy mala suerte!</string>
    <string name="sample_text">Sample text!</string>

</resources>